[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "That's pretty close to it, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What is your reaction to this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, my reaction is that I think it's been very clear now for quite a long time that there was no demonstration and that of course was the key element in what Ambassador Rice was saying and what the president was saying, and all about this hateful video and the demonstrations that it triggered.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "White House", "Libyan National Assembly"], "PERSON": ["Bob Schieffer"]}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "EX", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Do you dispute that she acted in good faith in reporting what she had been told by the CIA intelligence briefing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, I know this that on the same day when she was at all of these different Sunday shows, sent out by the White House and with talking points from the White House, immediate -- the show that I was on, \"Face the Nation,\" immediately after she gave her standard statement there, they -- Bob Schieffer had the president of the Libyan National Assembly on.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rumsfeld"], "LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "And I suppose the obvious question is, is it fair to impugn the integrity of the U.N. ambassador if she was genuinely acting in good faith on the CIA briefing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, you covered a lot of territory there and I would like to point out I'm the guy that called for Rumsfeld to resign because the war in Iraq was going terribly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.N.", "CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Clearly if the CIA had been inaccurately briefing for quite some time after this, do you believe that he should be accountable for the misinformation process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Everybody should be accountable, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "What is your take on this and what do you think the American reaction should be, if anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Well, I think the whole area is unraveling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Should Mitt Romney be a little above this now and just take defeat gracefully?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Over the fact you hadn't gone to a briefing about Benghazi, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Why you weren't at that meeting yesterday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "CCAIN: Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gaza"]}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Fred, what's the latest there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "What we're seeing overhead is basically Israeli war planes flying towards the border with Gaza.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What is your sense of how this is playing out in the international stage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "It's very difficult to assess who's at fault for this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "What are you hearing and what is the plan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I won't get into military operations but it has to be very, very clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "What is the constructive way through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I want to make something perfectly clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "It's a dangerous cocktail, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "That's precisely it, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Is that at risk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "It's very much at risk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "It's an awful place for people to try and live, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "First, one has to say, Piers, as you did, the Israelis are justified in doing something when all these rockets are being fired at them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I think it's very clear that the administration didn't handle things right from the start.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "WP", "NN", "RB", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "What was your reaction, honestly, to what Mitt Romney was saying there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, my reaction really for all of the elections around the country is it's really time to sort of evaluate what went right and what went wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "If I was a black or Hispanic or female voter, I would be like, hang on a second, he's saying what, we've been bought?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Well, look, Piers, you said something that frustrates me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "In the spirit of cooperation, how do you feel about somebody like Senator McCain making it so personal towards Ambassador Rice about what happened in Benghazi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Well, look, what's important about Benghazi is to really get to the heart of the matter, truly understand what went wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["McCain"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "What are you going to do next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "What was he to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, he was that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "What would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Yeah, I mean if it was like choosing a favorite child, then I would have been the most profligate woman on the planet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "``", "JJ", "CD", ",", "''", "``", "JJ", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "How do you think he would have liked to have been remembered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "As somebody who said, which he said in the front of the -- the beginning of his memoir, \"Hitch 22,\" \"live all you can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]